Let's go, Galgal Channel GO!
GO!
Today I would like to play a guessing game.
In this game, there will be one contestant and two respondents, and the contestant will play a song through earphones while gesturing the lyrics or expressing the sound, and we, the audience, will try to guess the song we are listening to.
Can I dance?
No, you can't.
We would be exposed.
That sounds difficult.
You are not allowed to dance, are you?
If I really can't guess, I'll make it a bit more difficult.
For now, I would like to guess only with gestures and expressions, without dancing.
Expression is becoming more and more important.
You are expressive, aren't you?
Do you?
You have to be assertive.
But I started out as an actress.
Sakura, I'll be watching here.
I'll leave it to Minami.
Why Mee?
At first I thought you would start with Me.
Then let's go in this order.
Me first.
You can't guess.
Please try to guess as you watch.
Let's start the video!
This time, I am wearing a costume by D-Holic.
The costume is worn by the staff as shown here.
Okay, then, let's start with Minami.
Please start from Minami.
Can you understand it?
This is a song that everyone knows.
Who doesn't know it? Oh, my God. That's how good you are?
I'm pretty sure I know this one at least.
Okay, I got it.
I'm sure.
I'll have a drink soon.
Okay.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Oni? eh?
I'll tell you.
I hear it's singing now.
Yes!
But can you do it for me? Dance? I'm not sure.
I'm not sure about this either.
Pepper's been talking about it a lot more.
I'm sorry, but that's what you'll be doing on the 8th, Eagle!
Egg, take this, take this...
I said I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm going. I'm going to go get dressed.
You look cute. I miss it. Yay!
The rhythm is a little slow.
So who's singing?
Uh, Louko.
I'm fine.
I'm walking.
Books my baby
Job and jolly days
Whisper, whisper, whisper.
What do you mean?
Let's play.
I don't know, it just sounds like that when Minami sings.
I don't know.
Happy, happy, happy, happy, children, happy, children, happy, children.
That's it,
Number 2, next.
What don't you get?
I definitely don't know the song.
Wait, wait, wait. What was that?
What is it?
I don't know this one either.
Try me. Say it.
A walk?
Let's see...
Boom.
You don't have to say it.
What?
I thought it was some kind of gallevo, but it's not.
Looks like an electric horse.
What's that walking thing?
It's walking around the gap, like this. No?
No, no.
Uh, number two, let's just go on from here.
Let's start walking.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Rust, you're coming. You're coming.
Eh, you know the two?
You are my soulmate
No, I'm only going to add a little more to the chorus, so don't sing it.
What? What?
Uncool. No!
No existing chorus?
No. No?
I don't know. I don't know too much.
What?
Oops.
My baby.
No, no, no, no.No no no.
On TikTok.
It's even more confusing.
All Japanese know.
OK.
I don't know.
I don't know, it's hard to express.
I don't know, I'm not afraid.
No, it's not.
You're doing lyrics.
Hmm?
I thought it didn't make sense.
No! I'll tell you!
No!
Here!
Heartbreak?
Yous?
Archant?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore! It's a lift!
Really?
Anpanman March.
Only love
And courage
Is my friend.
Wow, you mean that?
How does Anpanman express that?
Anpanman.
Fly! Fly! Everywhere.
You're a hero.
I've found it.
Everybody's dream
To protect
Hey, hey, hey.
Be born
Born
You'll never know unless you do it.
Wow.
Oh, but from here
This is
Rhythm
Right here.
I got it right.
It's hard, it's hard
Anpanman March is so hard
What should I do?
Oh, no!
Why won't it come out?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, I don't know if I get it now.
Oh, that's what it looks like.
Please, please, please.
I'm Yuzu.
Yuzu-san.
Oh, early.
Wait a minute.
Ah,
It's Mickey.
It's Mickey! It's Mickey!
Jumbo! Jumbo!
Jamboree!
Jamboree Mickey!
I got the intro wrong.
This is all I got.
Wait a minute. Curve mistake.
I kind of messed that up.
Isn't it too fast?
But, I mean, isn't it strong?
He's throwing it, he's throwing it, he's throwing it.
That was Jumbali Mickey.
That was too fast.
I'm sorry. Let me try again.
But you got it.
It's Mickey!
I mean, come on, Mipmoo.
Okay, here we go.
I'm doing the intro.
But I need to know the rhythm of the intro.
Isn't it slow?
What?
It hurts.
Oh, I don't know, it just came out.
Not at all.
Hungry?
Shangri-La.
There's something around here.
It's like... it's like... it's like...
Like a broken heart or something?
Oh, she's crying.
What?
It's a song about getting over a broken heart, isn't it?
I'm a new person, right?
Did you change? I did.
Like Kana Nishino.
She's cute.
It's frustrating.
You know, right?
You've been flying for a long time.
She's transforming.
When you shake your head.At the time of something
I said it's hot.
Your mouth is hot.
I'm walking again.
I'm lost again.
It's a new time.
Oh, my God.
I'm not kidding.
dj
plutôt porn
Ocr.
You know what?
He went down a hole.
Went down a hole.
What's that?
Red Little?
That's right!
Ooh!
Lady Vaux! Lady Vaux!
That's why you were woged?
Isn't it amazing?
What is that? This.
Something that's been bothering you.
The A melody, the B melody, it's so negative.
That's why I was morphing.
It was embarrassing.
Even when I run like this.
It's like, "I'm going to show up.
Isn't that great?
It's amazing!
Like a fine play.
That's amazing!
I was looking for something with a little bit of flight.
Maybe it was flying.
It was flying.
Isn't that great?
How do you say, "Caught in the wind"?
Like this.
Like that?
That's what that is?
It looked like a construction site to me.
That's great.
Thanks for the two songs.
Jumbo and Mikiban.
Jumbo?
Yes, that's right,
You're done.
It was hard to count.
I don't know how to express myself,
I should have listened more.
It was fun.
Yes, it was fun.
Yes, so thank you very much for watching.
If you liked this video, please give it a high rating,
If you liked this video, please give it a high rating, leave a comment and subscribe to my channel.
Bye bye!